JAMSHID KHOSRAVI

WEB DEVELOPER



✓ jamshid.khosravi1993@gmail.com

Magdeburg, Germany (Open to Relocation)

Portfolio (https://jimikhosravi.github.io/)

LinkedIn (https://www.linkedin.com/in/jamshidkhos ravi/)

GitHub (https://github.com/JimiKhosravi/)

SKILLS & TOOLS

Front-End:

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript
- · React, Angular, React Native
- Bootstrap library
- jQuery
- Responsive Design

Back-End & Databases:

- Python
- Django
- Node.js
- Express
- RESTful APIs
- Relational Databases (MySQL & PostgreSQL)
 & Non-Relational Databases (MongoDB)
- JSON

Also proficient in:

- Git
- Test-Driven Development (Jest & Supertest)
 & Behavior-Driven Development (BDD)
- Postman
- Heroku & Netlify (PaaS)
- Agile (Trello)
- Docker (familiarity)

Languages:

- English
- Persian

PROFILE

Web developer with a background in Civil Engineering and Water Engineering. Experienced in supervising the construction of structures and collaborating effectively within interdisciplinary teams. Innovative problem-solver with a strong drive for continuous learning and acquiring new skills.

EXPERIENCE

Trainee web developer | CareerFoundry, Berlin, Germany, September 2022 - May 2023

- Intense project-based training program focused on JavaScript, Python, HTML, CSS and most prominent libraries, frameworks and tools.
- 500+ hours of hands-on training with guidance of industry leading tutor and mentor.
- Developed myFlix App: created a non-relational database (MongoDB) for movies, built REST APIs using Node.js and Express, tested them with Postman and deployed the app on Heroku.

Executive engineer | Hafar Khak Combaden | Tehran, Iran, July 2016 - August 2020

- Control of accurate execution of works technically.
- Implement the project schedule and control it.
- Getting executive plans from the technical office to implement them and giving them to the executors.
- Continuous communication with the site manager and giving a detailed report of the works.

Teaching assistant for "Surveying and Operations" | Iran University of Science and Technology, Tehran, Iran, October 2013 - March 2014

• Conducted practice-solving classes.

Math Private Tutor | Tehran, Iran, August 2016 - January 2020

· Provided high school students with math tutoring.

Volunteer work:

Taught Math and Science to cancer children | Bahrami Hospital, Tehran, Iran, February 2015 - October 2015

EDUCATION

Certificate in Full-Stack Web Development | CareerFoundry, Berlin, Germany, September 2022 - May 2023

M.E. Water Engineering | Magdeburg-Stendal University of Applied Sciences, Magdeburg, Germany, October 2020 - Present

B.S. Civil Engineering | Iran University of Science and Technology,

Tehran, Iran, September 2011 - May 2016